Contact

Sitara Sapna City Daewo Road ,Faisalabad Pakistan 03037498388 (Mobile) sarmadsaeed13@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sarmadsaeed-865aa912a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ASP.NET MVC

jQuery

SQL Server Management Studio

Sarmad Saeed

Software Engineer at NETSOL Technologies Inc. Lahore District

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Angular, React, Redux, Nest JS, Jquery, Typeorm, Entity framrwork core orm,C#, .Net Core, .NET Framework MVC, Micro Services, WPF, MVVM, WCF,Javascript,Web API,MS SQL SERVER,Azure Cosmos db, Azure Storage Tables,Microsoft Bot Composer, Azure LUIS, Azure QnA maker, ASTM standards, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Bootstrap, and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS). Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Computer Science focused in Computer Programming from National University of Computer and Emerging Sciences.

Experience

NETSOL Technologies Inc.
Software Engineer
February 2020 - Present (1 year 9 months)
Lahore, Pakistan

NTG (National Technology Group)
Software Engineer
July 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 8 months)
Lahore, Pakistan

Education

National University of Computer and Emerging Sciences
Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Programming (2013 - 2018)